Stylish Privacy Policy
======================

Last Modified: August 4, 2024
-----------------------------

We are Similarweb and this is our privacy policy for our Stylish product and service. If you have read privacy policies before, you may have found that they are difficult to understand and often overwhelm you with information. As such, we will try to keep this simple and get to the bottom line right away: **We do not want to know your identity and we do not automatically collect data to try and figure out who you are**. Of course, we need to give you all of the regular privacy policy information to which you are entitled, and we will get to that in a minute. But first, and in case you do not have the time or patience to read through the whole policy, we want to repeat and make that point perfectly clear: We do not **want to know your identity** - unless you decide to share it by registering on our website or contacting us for support, in which case we will use it **only for that purpose.**  
  
In the rest of this privacy policy, we are going to give you a lot of detail about exactly what data is collected from you, how it is processed, where it is stored, and what your rights are as a user. That is important information, and we certainly hope you carefully read the entire policy. As a user of a product from which data is processed, you are entitled to that information and we are obligated to make it available. That makes sense and is as it should be since you deserve to be protected from intrusive data practices. Compliance with data privacy laws and regulations, including the GDPR, is extremely important to us and is a top priority in our activities as a global company.  
  
Sure, we do collect information from you when you use our product. The information is collected using code that is open-source and which can be inspected by anyone capable of doing so. We realize that most users may not be able to read that code, but the point is, the purpose of that data collection is to provide you with the best Stylish product and service we can. We have no interest in knowing the identity of any individual users, and we invest enormous resources to ensure that we are not able to do so (for example, we use an algorithm designed to remove from collected browser data any personal information that may have been inadvertently included in it). We also delete from IP addresses the portion that provides specific geolocation information.  
  
If you got this far, we hope you will continue and read the rest of this policy. Either way, if you decide to use our Stylish product or services and have any questions about your rights as a user, feel free to contact us at [support@userstyles.org](mailto:support@userstyles.org,),  
  
As data protection is important to us, we have engaged an external data privacy expert to serve as our Data Protection Officer. If you have any questions regarding this policy or your data privacy rights, you are welcome to contact our Data Protection Officer at:  

**MyEDPO**

Unit 3D North Point House

North Point Business Park

New Mallow Road

Cork T23AT2P

IRELAND

Website: [www.myedpo.com](https://www.myedpo.com/)

Email: dpo@userstyles.org

This Privacy Policy governs the data processing practices of Similarweb Ltd. ("**Company**," "**Similarweb**," "**we**," "**our**" or "**us**") in connection with: (i) our visitor’s use (“Visitor”) of our website [https://userstyles.org](https://userstyles.org/) (“**Website**”); or (ii) the users of our Stylish browser extension or mobile application (“Stylish Product”) or our services included therein (“**Services**” and “**users**,” respectively). The Website, Stylish Product and the Services shall be referred to collectively herein as the “**Stylish Platform**”. Each of the Visitors and Users are collectively referred to within this Privacy Policy as “you” or “**your**”.  
  
If you would like to learn more about our Services and the Stylish Platform please review our [Terms of Use](https://userstyles.org/terms-of-use) ("**Terms of Use**") which governs your use of the Website, Service or the Stylish Platform (as applicable).  
  
We have included information below about what data is collected and how we process and use your data, but first we would like to explain the lawful basis that we rely on to do so:  

1) Where you sign up for any of our Services, we process your data based on the necessity to provide those services and in order to perform our **contract** with you;

2) If we have a **legitimate interest** in processing data, such as for direct marketing (i.e., sending you updates about our service after you have registered) or using online identifiers when you access our Website;

3) We will also process your Personal Information where you have provided us with your **consent** to do so.

We reserve the right to periodically amend or revise the Privacy Policy at our sole discretion. Such changes and updates will be effective immediately upon the display of the revised Privacy Policy. Thus, we encourage you to check this Privacy Policy regularly for updates, so that you are fully informed of how your data is collected and used by the Company and your related rights. The last revision date will be reflected in the "Last Modified" heading. In the event of material changes that will adversely affect your use of the Stylish Product or Service or the data collection by us, we will make best efforts to provide you with notification through the Website or Service.  
  
IF YOU ANY OF OUR DATA PROCESSING PRACTICES EXPLAINED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY ARE UNACCEPTABLE TO YOU PLEASE DO NOT ACCESS OR USE THE WEBSITE, DOWNLOAD, INSTALL, OR USE THE STYLISH PRODUCT OR SERVICES IN ANY MANNER.  
  
**WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT AND HOW DO WE USE IT?**  
  
We collect non-identifiable aggregated information which is made available via your use of the Stylish Platform ("**Non-Personal Information**"), which does not allow us to determine the identity of the users from whom the Non-Personal Information is collected. In some cases, such as when you register on our Website, we also collect identifiable information, namely information that may with reasonable effort be used to identify an individual ("**Personal Information**"). Additionally, depending on your browser settings or the cookie settings you have chosen, Personal Information may be collected when you visit our Website, via our third-party cookies as shall be further explained below.  
  
In the event we combine Personal Information with Non-Personal Information, the combined information will be treated as Personal Information for as long as it remains combined.  

| **Type of Information** | **How We Use It & Legal Basis** | **Opt Out** |
| --- | --- | --- |
| We process IP addresses or other online identifiers (“**Online Identifiers**”). Note that IP addresses are accessed automatically every time a device visits a website. We consider and treat Online Identifiers as Personal Information, in accordance with applicable laws. | We may either directly or indirectly (i.e., via cookies) collect Visitors’ Online Identifiers. We use this for our legitimate interests of: (i) operating, providing, maintaining, protecting, and managing our Website; (ii) enhancing your experience; and (iii) our legitimate interests of auditing and tracking our Website’s usage statistics.  <br>  <br>We may also use this information for analytic purposes based on your consent when your consent is required in accordance with applicable law. | You have certain cookie controls that may be made available to you via our Website. Please see our ”Cookies and Tracking Technologies” section below for more information on how to opt out and change your browser or cookies preferences. |
| We collect certain technical information which relates to your use of the Website such as your page views, type of browser, and time and date of use. Such information may be associated with your Online Identifier. | It is our legitimate interest to use this technical data in order to operate and manage our Website. |     |
| While using the Website, you are able to upload certain content to the Website (“**User Generated Content**” or “**UGC**”). User Generated Content refers to a wide variety of content that is produced by you and other users of the Service, as opposed to content generated by us. The UGC may include Web Styles, images, comments, posts, texts, icons, links, opinions and feedback provided by you and by other users of the Website and Services. By exchanging, providing or uploading UGC, you grant us permission to use, store and process the aforesaid content, including any of your Personal Information that are contained therein (e.g., comments, rates, etc.). | You may voluntarily upload User Generated Content to the Website. In the event that the User Generated Content includes any Personal Information, by uploading it you grant us your consent to process the aforesaid content, including any Personal Information that are contained therein (e.g., comments, rates). We will solely use the UGC to display it in our Website and our Stylish Products, and will not process or store it for any other purpose.  <br>  <br>You should be aware that any UGC or other information you voluntarily upload to the Website may be read, collected, and used by others who access the Website, forum or Stylish Services. | To request the removal of your Personal Information from our Website or community forum, contact us at: nformation We Collect from Stylish Mobile App Users and your opt-out opt[contact@userstyles.org](mailto:contact@userstyles.org,) |
| We may have third-party advertising partners’ cookies on our Website. Such third-party Cookies may collect your Online Identifiers, as well as an advertising ID or Cookie ID (i.e., an identification number that is unique to the device or the browser that you use when you access our Website). These third- party cookies may also have access to additional information associated with your use of our Website, for example, the content you view while on our Website. Our advertising partners may combine this aforementioned information with information they have collected from other sources, such as other websites that you visit or have visited. | This data is collected by our third-party advertising partners in order to deliver advertisements to you, including personalized advertisements. It may also be used by such partners to build a profile of your interests and show you advertisements on other third party's sites. Subject to applicable laws in your jurisdiction, when you access our Website we may request your consent to enable data collection for advertising purposes. | You have certain controls on your cookies preferences, including by using the cookies management tool in our website. See our "Cookies and Tracking Technologies" section below for more information on how to opt out and change your cookies preferences. |
| If you wish to sign up and open an account through the Website at: [https://userstyles.org/login](https://userstyles.org/login) you will be requested to provide us with certain information such as a your user name, email address, and password, at which time you thereby represent and warrant that you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your details and password. You may also choose to sign in with one of your social networks such as Google, Yahoo or OpenID. Such network account may give us access to certain information about you as stored therein (e.g., full name, e-mail and any other information which you made public) in accordance with their terms. | If you wish to sign up and open an account through the Website at: [https://userstyles.org/login](https://userstyles.org/login) you will be requested to provide us with certain information such as a your user name, email address, and password, at which time you thereby represent and warrant that you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your details and password. You may also choose to sign in with one of your social networks such as Google, Yahoo or OpenID. Such network account may give us access to certain information about you as stored therein (e.g., full name, e-mail and any other information which you made public) in accordance with their terms. | To request the removal of your Personal Information from our Website or community forum, contact us at: [contact@userstyles.org](mailto:contact@userstyles.org,). |
| In the event you contact us for support or other inquiries, either through our [online form](https://userstyles.org/contact) available | on the Website, by sending us an email or by other means of communications we make available, you will be requested to provide us your name and email address. | To request the removal of your Personal Information from our Website or community forum, contact us at: [contact@userstyles.org](mailto:contact@userstyles.org,). |

**Information We Collect From Stylish Extension Users and your opt-out options**  
This information is processed if you install and use our Stylish browser extension:  

| **Type of Information** | **How We Use It & Legal Basis** | **Opt Out** |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Standard web server log information (i.e., page views). In order to avoid receiving and processing any Personal Information, we use an advanced cleaning algorithm designed to filter from browsing data any information that could be used to determine the identity of a user. | We use this information to support and enable the Stylish services (i.e., to understand how popular websites are in order for us to determine which websites, and which sections within each website, we would want to build and support Web Styles).  <br>  <br>We may also use this information for market intelligence purposes and to develop insights-based products and services, which we then may provide to our clients and customers. We will use this information for this purpose when you provide us with your consent for us to do so, if we are required to under applicable law. | Right click on the extension icon, select 'Options', and uncheck the box that says "Send de-identified browsing data to Stylish to access style suggestions through the toolbar menu" and/or uncheck the box that says "Send de- identified SERP data to Stylish to access style suggestions on search results" and/or uncheck the box that says "Show number of styles active for the current site on the toolbar button" and/or uncheck the box that says "Send feedback in the format of usage analytics to help us improve Stylish".  <br>  <br>Note that once you opt out, part of the Services provided by the Stylish browser extension will no longer be available, meaning "Suggested Web Styles" won't be available in the browser extension interface, and "Suggested Web Styles" won’t be available in the context menu. |
| AI inputs and outputs which includes any prompts, queries, content, uploaded files (e.g., images, videos, text CSV files) and other inputs that you may enter or submit to certain artificial intelligence (AI) tools, as well as the results or other outputs (including any attached files included in such outputs) that you may receive from such AI tools (collectively, “**AI Inputs and Outputs**”). Considering the nature and general scope of input and output that is typical to AI tools, some sensitive personal data may be inadvertently processed in the provision of our Services. However, the aim of the processing is not the collection of any Personal Information or data that could identify you. While we cannot guarantee that all Personal Information is removed, we do take steps to remove or filter out identifiers and personal data that you may enter or submit to these tools. | We use the AI inputs and outputs to provide the Company’s services and solutions. The legal basis for our processing of the AI Inputs and Outputs is based on your consent, where such consent is required by applicable laws. To the extent sensitive personal data is inadvertently processed as part of the AI Inputs and Outputs, such data will be processed on the basis of your explicit consent, where required by applicable law. | You can withdraw your consent at any time as detailed below through the opt-out options. You can opt-out of the collection of the AI Inputs and outputs by following the instructions in the “User Rights” section below. |
| Non-personal Technical information such as your interaction with the extension (e.g., installed Styles), browser type, operating system, device model name, device screen size, time and date. We further collect IP Address (trimmed for anonymization). | We use this for: (i) operating, providing, maintaining, protecting, and managing our Stylish Product and Service; (ii) enhancing your experience; and (iii) our legitimate interests of auditing and tracking usage statistics. |     |

**Information We Collect from Stylish Mobile App Users and your opt-out options**  
This information is collected and processed if you install and use our Stylish mobile app:  

| **Type of Information** | **How We Use It & Legal Basis** | **Opt Out** |
| --- | --- | --- |
| We collect standard non- personal web server log information (i.e., page views), search results data (keyword, order/index of results, links of results, title, description, and ads displayed). In order to avoid processing any Personal Information, we use an advanced cleaning algorithm designed to remove any information that could be used to determine the identity of a user from browsing data. | We use this information to support and enable the Stylish services (i.e., to understand how popular websites are in order for us to determine for which website, and for which sections within each website, we will want to build and support Styles). | Uninstall the mobile app directly from your device or through the app page on the applicable mobile application store. Note, that once you uninstall the app, customization of the Navigation Bar and Widgets provided by the Stylish app will not be available for your device. After you opt out, we will no longer automatically collect and share your Non-Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy. |
| We also collect your IP Address - which is accessed automatically every time there is communication between a device and a server - which we trim for anonymization. | IP Address is trimmed to remove specific geo-location information and is used only to determine the country in which the user is located. |     |
| Information regarding installed applications and their use. | We use this information to personalize the Stylish services (i.e., to understand how popular websites/apps are in order for us to determine for which websites/apps, and for which sections within each website, we will want to build and support Styles). |     |

**HOW WE COLLECT INFORMATION**  
**Depending on the nature of your interaction with the Stylish Platform**, we may collect information as follows:  

* **Automatically -** we may directly or indirectly (i.e., by using cookies as further explained in the section below) gather information automatically, such as Non-Personal Information as well as Online Identifiers.
* **Provided by you voluntarily -** we will collect Personal Information if you choose to register or if you contact us for support.

**COOKIES**  
When you access or use the Website, or interact with our Services, we may use “cookies” (or similar technologies), which store certain information on your device (i.e., locally stored) and which will allow us to customize the Service and content as well as enhance your experience of the Services. The use of cookies is a standard industry-wide practice. A "cookie" is a small piece of information that a website assigns and stores on your device while you are viewing a website. Cookies are very helpful and can be used for various purposes such as allowing you to navigate between pages efficiently and making the interaction between you and our Services quicker and easier.  
  
We may permit third parties to use cookies or other technology to collect information about your online and application usage activities across our Services. This information may include Online Identifiers, and therefore we recommend you review the cookie policies for the relevant third-party cookies carefully:  

| **Cookie** | **Purpose** | **Link to service** |
| --- | --- | --- |
| **Google Analytics** | Analytical, Measurement & Performance | [www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners) |
| **Doubleclick.net** | Targeting & Advertising |     |
| **Bing.com** | Analytical, Measurement & Performance and Targeting & Advertising | [https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/privacystatement](https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/privacystatement) |
| **Clarity.ms** | Analytical, Measurement & Performance and Targeting & Advertising |     |
| **Facebook** | Analytical, Measurement & Performance and Targeting & Advertising | [https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/previous](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/previous)  <br>[https://www.facebook.com/policies/cookies/](https://www.facebook.com/policies/cookies/) |
| **Twitter** | Only for the sake of sharing a style on the userstyles.org website | [https://twitter.com/en/privacy](https://twitter.com/en/privacy) |
| **PayPal** | Only for the sake of donating to style creators on userstyles.org | [https://optout.aboutads.info](https://optout.aboutads.info/) |

HOW IS THE DATA SHARED OR TRANSFERRED?  
We may disclose Personal Information to the following parties for the following purposes:  

1. **Vendors and Service Providers.** We may share Personal Information we collect with our service providers, processors, and vendors who perform functions on our behalf to allow us to provide the Services (for example: cloud hosting providers, payment processors, etc.).
2. **Business Partners.** We may also share certain Personal Information as necessary prior to the completion of a transaction or corporate transactions such as financings, restructurings, merger or acquisition transactions, to lenders, auditors, and third-party advisors, including attorneys and consultants, as part of due diligence or as necessary to plan for a transaction.
3. **SimilarWeb Customers:** We may compile and disclose analytics and market intelligence data derived from the data we collect about you and other users through the Services. Generally, the data that we disclose to customers is aggregated and converted into metrics that do not identify you. In limited cases, we may disclose your Personal Information to our clients so that they may conduct their own analysis on consumer behaviors; however, we contractually prohibit them from using this data in order to reach you with targeted advertising or from further sharing or disclosing this data to third parties.
4. **Others, as permitted or required by applicable law.** We may disclose Personal Information to third parties (authorities, legal representatives, regulators, government entities, and law enforcement) to the extent permitted or required by applicable laws. It may also include certain disclosures that we are required to make. We may disclose your Personal Information when we believe it is appropriate to do so to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person, violations of our [Terms of Use](https://userstyles.org/terms-of-use) or this Privacy Policy, or as evidence in litigation in which we are involved.

DATA TRANSFERS  
We may store or process your Personal Information in the UK, the EU, the United States or in other countries. As such, please be advised that any information you provide us may be transferred to and processed in countries other than the country from which you accessed our Website or Services. We will make sure to implement appropriate measures to ensure that your Personal Information receives an adequate level of data protection while it is being transferred. When Personal Information that was  
  
collected within the European Economic Area (“**EEA**”) or the UK is transferred outside the EEA or the UK (as applicable), we will take necessary steps in order to ensure that sufficient safeguards are provided during the transferring of such Personal Information. You may exercise your rights, where applicable, to receive information regarding the transfer mechanism that was used during the transferring of your Personal Information. Personal Information that is being transferred outside the EEA to a country which has not received an adequacy decision from the European Commission (“**Adequacy Decision**”) will be transferred pursuant to the [standard contractual clauses](https://commission.europa.eu/law/law-topic/data-protection/international-dimension-data-protection/standard-contractual-clauses-scc_en) approved by the European Union (“**Standard Contractual Clauses**”). Personal Information that we transfer outside of the UK to a country that is not in the EEA, has not received an Adequacy Decision or an adequacy regulation has not been passed regarding it by the UK will be transferred, depending on the situation, either pursuant to the [International Data Transfer Agreement](https://ico.org.uk/media/for-organisations/documents/4019538/international-data-transfer-agreement.pdf) or the [addendum](https://ico.org.uk/media/for-organisations/documents/4019539/international-data-transfer-addendum.pdf) to be used with the Standard Contractual Clauses, both as issued by the UK’s Information Commissioner.  
  
DATA RETENTION  
Please note that, unless you instruct us otherwise, we retain the information we collect for as long as needed to provide the Services and to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements. If you object to the aforesaid collection, use and sharing of data, please immediately cease using the Service and remove the Stylish Product from your device. The data we receive in the event you access our Website, Stylish Product or Service via a third-party social or other network depends on your privacy settings with the network (e.g., Gmail, Yahoo) and you should always review, and if necessary, adjust your privacy settings on third-party websites and services before linking or connecting them to our Service.  
  
USER RIGHTS FOR EEA AND UK RESIDENTS  
  
Depending on your jurisdiction, data protection and privacy laws may provide you with the ability to exercise certain rights with respect to your Personal Information. We have included the rights that apply to EEA and UK residents below for your reference and convenience. If you are a California resident, please see our Privacy Information for California Residents Section below for a description of your privacy rights.  

1. **Right to Access:** You may have the right to access your Personal Information by asking us to confirm what Personal Information we process about you, as well as additional information regarding how and the purposes for such processing, and to request and obtain a copy of such Personal Information.
2. **Right to be Informed:** You have the right to be informed regarding Embee’s information (e.g., our name and address) as well as what Personal Information we process, and how and why we process Personal Information.
3. **Right to Rectification:** You may have the right to require us to update and complete any Personal Information that we have about you that is inaccurate or incomplete and to require us to inform third parties that process such Personal Information on our behalf to update such inaccurate or incomplete data.
4. **Right to Erasure:** You may have the right, depending on the circumstances, to request that we delete your Personal Information that is held by us. We are not required to comply with your request to erase Personal Information if the processing of your Personal Information is necessary for our compliance with a legal obligation; or the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims.
5. **Right to Restrict the Processing: Depending** on the circumstances, you may have the right to limit the purposes for which we process your Personal Information. We can continue to use your Personal Information following your request to restrict the processing of your Personal Information, where we have your consent; or to establish, exercise or defend legal claims; or to protect the rights of another natural or legal person.
6. **Right to Data Portability:** You may have the right to request that we send or “port” the Personal Information that we process about you to a third-party, but in each case only where the processing is based on your consent or on the performance of a contract with you, and the processing is carried out by automated means. It is important to note that the GDPR and the CCPA differ in the application of this right and therefore we will handle the fulfillment according to the applicable laws in your jurisdiction
7. **Right to Object:** You may have the right to object to the processing of your Personal Information on the basis of our legitimate interest. The right to object does not exist, in particular, if the processing of your Personal Information is necessary in order to enter into a contract with you or to perform a contract with you.
8. **Right to Object to Direct Marketing:** You can request that we change the manner in which we contact you for marketing purposes. You can request that we not transfer your Personal Information to unaffiliated third parties for the purposes of direct marketing or any other purpose.
9. **Right to Withdraw Consent:** If you have given us your consent for the processing of your Personal Information, you may have the right to withdraw your consent at any time, without affecting the lawfulness of processing based on consent before your consent was withdrawn.
10. **Data Transfer Rights:** You may be able to obtain a copy of, or reference to, the safeguards under which your Personal Information is being transferred outside the UK/EEA. We have included links and explanations regarding these mechanisms in the Data Transfers S above.
11. **Rights in relation to automated decision making and profiling:** You may have the right to not be subject to a decision based solely on automatic decision making or profiling.

Where you believe that we have not complied with our obligation under this Privacy Policy, the GDPR, or the UK data protection laws, you have the right to make a complaint to an EU Data Protection Authority or the UK Information Commissioner's Office (as applicable).  
  
To assert any of these rights, please contact our Data Protection Officer at: dpo@userstyles.org. Note that we may request proof of identity, and we reserve the right to charge a fee where allowed by law, such as in circumstances where your request is excessive. In addition, you may have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority, subject to applicable law (as is the case in the European Union).  
  
HOW DO WE SAFEGUARD YOUR INFORMATION?  
We employ industry standard procedures and policies to ensure the safety of our users’ information and prevent unauthorized use thereof. We have implemented technical, physical and administrative security measures to protect the Personal Information, including without limitation by using industry standard encryption. In addition, we limit access to your information on our servers. The data collected by us is stored in the AWS data servers; for more information regarding the data security provided by AWS, please see: [https://aws.amazon.com/security/](https://aws.amazon.com/security/). Although we take reasonable steps to safeguard information, we cannot be responsible for the acts of those who gain unauthorized access or abuse Company’s Services, and we make no warranty, express, implied or otherwise, that we will prevent such access. Further, in the event of a data incident, in which we discover your Personal Information may be at risk, then we will take reasonable efforts to notify you and the applicable authority (if required, subject to applicable laws).  
  
MINORS  
Our Services are not directed or intended for children, as follows: (i) US residents under 13 years of age; (ii) EU residents under 16 years of age; or (iii) as children are otherwise defined under applicable law. We will not knowingly solicit, collect and store Personal Information directly from children. If you are under 18, please be sure to read the terms of this Privacy Policy with your parents or legal guardians. If we later obtain actual knowledge that a user is considered a child under applicable law, we will take steps to immediately delete its Personal Information. We request that such individuals do not provide Personal Information through the Services. If you become aware or have any reason to believe that a child has shared any information with us, please contact us at: [dpo@userstyles.org](mailto:dpo@userstyles.org,).  
  
PRIVACY INFORMATION FOR CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS  
In this section, we provide information for California residents, as required under the California privacy laws, including the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”), which requires that we provide California residents certain specific information about how we handle their personal information, whether collected online or offline. Under the CCPA, “Personal Information” is any information that identifies, relates to, describes, is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular California resident or household. It does not include publicly available data as defined by the CCPA. This section does not address or apply to our handling of publicly available information made lawfully available by state or federal governments or other personal information that is subject to an exemption under Section 1798.145(c) – (f) of the CCPA.  
  
Except for the right to opt-out and the right of non-discrimination, this section does not apply to California residents with whom we transact or communicate solely in the context of providing or receiving a product or service to or from a company that employs such residents or engages such residents as contractors. This section also does not apply to personal information we collect about job applicants, independent contractors, or current or former full-time, part-time and temporary employees and staff, officers, directors or owners of SimilarWeb or any affiliated entities.  
  
CATEGORIES OF PERSONAL INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT, DISCLOSE, AND SELL  

| **Categories of Personal Information Collected** | **Third Party Disclosures for Business or Commercial Purposes** |
| --- | --- | --- |
| **Identifiers.** Includes direct identifiers, such as name, alias, account number or unique personal identifier; email address, phone number, and other contact information; IP address and other online identifiers. | * Advisors and agents<br>* Security and fraud prevention providers<br>* Business customers<br>* Others as required by law |
| **Customer Records.** Includes information such as name, user ID, account name, contact information, and other similar information. For example, this may include information collected when an individual signs up for our Services. | * Advisors and agents<br>* Security and fraud prevention providers<br>* Regulators, government entities and law enforcement<br>* Others as required by law |
| **Commercial Information.** Includes records of products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or use histories or tendencies. | * Advisors and agents<br>* Business customers<br>* Security and fraud prevention providers<br>* Regulators, government entities and law enforcement<br>* Others as required by law |     |
| **Internet or Other Electronic Network Activity Information.** Includes but is not limited to, browsing history, clickstream data, search history, and information regarding interactions with our website and services, advertisements, including other usage data related to your use of any of our services or other similar online services. | * Advisors and agents<br>* Security and fraud prevention providers<br>* Business customers<br>* Others as required by law |     |
| **Profiles and Inferences.** Such as inferences drawn from any of the information described in this section about a consumer including inferences reflecting the consumer’s preferences, characteristics, behaviors, attitudes, abilities, and aptitudes. | * Affiliates and subsidiaries<br>* Regulators, government entities and law enforcement<br>* Others as required by law |     |
| **Sensitive Personal Information.** In some circumstances, since we generally collect information on all the URLs visited these may include URLs or visits to sensitive websites. Such sensitive websites may relate to religious or philosophical beliefs, consumer health related data, and information concerning a consumer’s sex life or sexual orientation. | * Business customers |     |

###### Sources of Personal Information:

We generally collect Personal Information from the following categories of sources: directly or indirectly from you; third parties; automatically, including personal information derived/inferred about users based upon their browsing or other data; and operations systems and platforms; business partners; vendors and service providers; publicly available sources; Internet service providers.

###### Collection, Use, and Disclosure:

* Operating Services and providing related support
* Analytics and improvement
* Communication
* Marketing, advertising, and campaign management
* Insight development and data enhancement
* Security and protection
* Business transfers
* Market intelligence or analytics services of our affiliates
* Compliance and legal process
* Auditing, reporting, and other internal operations
* Provision of Services by us and by our service providers, processors, and vendors
* General business and operational support

The CCPA defines a “sale” as disclosing or making available Personal Information to a third-party in exchange for monetary or other valuable consideration, and “sharing” includes disclosing or making available Personal Information to a third-party for purposes of cross-context behavioral advertising. We may “sell” or “share” the following categories of Personal Information: Identifiers, commercial information, internet and electronic network activity information, profiles and inferences, and sensitive personal information, as described above. We may “sell” or “share” these categories to business customers so that our business customers may better understand consumer behavior and analyze and improve their marketing and advertising campaigns.  
  
We do not sell or share personal information about individuals who we know are under age sixteen (16).  
  
CALIFORNIA CONSUMER RIGHTS  
California law grants consumers certain rights and imposes restrictions on particular business practices as set forth below. California consumers have the right to request that we disclose what personal information we collect, use, disclose, and sell about you, as further described below.  

* Right to Opt-out of a Sale of Personal Information ("Do Not Sell"):  
    California residents have the right to opt-out of our selling of their personal information. We do not process Personal Information for the purpose of targeted advertising or profiling and automated decision making.
* Requests for Copy, Deletion and Right to Know:  
    Subject to certain exceptions, California consumers have the right to make the following requests, at no charge, up to twice every 12 months. Please see "Submitting Requests" for instructions on how to exercise your rights.
* Deletion: California consumers have the right to request deletion of personal information that we have collected about you, subject to certain exemptions.
* Copy: California consumers have the right to request a copy of the specific pieces of personal information that we have collected about you in the prior 12 months.
* Right to Know (Collection): Where we have collected Personal Information about you, California consumers have the right to request that we disclose certain information about how we have handled your Personal Information in the 12 months prior to your request, including: the categories of Personal Information collected; categories of sources of Personal Information; business and/or commercial purposes for collecting and selling your Personal Information; and the categories of third parties/with whom we have disclosed or shared your Personal Information.
* Right to Know (Disclosure and Sale): Where we have sold or disclosed your Personal Information for a business purpose, California consumers have the right to request that we disclose certain information about how we have handled your Personal Information in the 12 months preceding your request, including: the categories of Personal Information collected; categories of third parties to whom your Personal Information has been sold and the specific categories of Personal Information sold to each category of third party; categories of third parties to whom Personal Information has been disclosed; and the categories of Personal Information that we have disclosed or shared with a third party for a business purpose.
* Submitting Requests. You can exercise your rights by emailing us at [dpo@userstyles.org](mailto:dpo@userstyles.org,). When you submit your request, we will take steps to attempt to verify your identity. We will seek to match the information in your request to the personal information we maintain about you. As part of our verification process, we may ask you to submit additional information, use identity verification services to assist us, or if you have created an account on our website or mobile app, we may ask you to sign in to your account as part of our identity verification process. Please understand that, depending on the type of request you submit, to protect the privacy and security of your personal information, we will only complete your request where we are satisfied that we have verified your identity to an appropriate degree of certainty. We will make every reasonable effort to respond to you within 45 days after we receive a verified request. If we are unable to meet this timescale, we will respond as soon as possible over the next 45-day period.

INCENTIVES AND DISCRIMINATION  
The CCPA prohibits discrimination against California consumers for exercising their rights under the CCPA and imposes requirements on any financial incentives offered to California consumers related to their personal information. Discrimination: if consumers exercise their rights under CCPA, businesses may not discriminate against them including by denying or providing a different level or quality of goods or services or charging or suggesting that a business will charge different prices or rates or impose penalties, unless doing so is reasonably related to the value provided to the consumer by the consumer’s data.  
  
CALIFORNIA’S SHINE-THE-LIGHT LAW  
Under California’s “Shine the Light” law (Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.83), California residents who provide us certain Personal Information are entitled to request and obtain from us, free of charge, information about the personal information (if any) we have shared with third parties for their own direct marketing use. Such requests may be made once per calendar year for information about any relevant third party sharing in the prior calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to [dpo@userstyles.org](mailto:dpo@userstyles.org,). In your request, please attest to the fact that you are a California resident. Your right to obtain information regarding any of your personal information we have shared with third parties for their own marketing use was included here solely in order to satisfy legal and regulatory notice requirements, we do not share any of your personal information with third parties for their own marketing use.  
  
ADDITIONAL PRIVACY INFORMATION FOR CERTAIN UNITED STATES RESIDENTS  

Residents of certain U.S. states, including Colorado, Connecticut, Virginia, and Utah, may have additional rights under applicable privacy laws and be entitled to additional disclosures.

**Sale of Personal Data:** We may sell the following categories of Personal Data: Identifiers, commercial information, internet and electronic network activity information, profiles and inferences, and “sensitive data,” as that term is defined under applicable U.S. privacy laws. We sell such categories of Personal Data to our business customers so that they may conduct their own analysis on consumer behaviors and analyze and improve their marketing and advertising campaigns.

**Consumer Rights:** Residents of certain U.S. states, including Colorado, Connecticut, Virginia, Washington, Nevada and Utah, may have additional rights under applicable privacy laws, subject to certain limitations, which may include:

* **Access.** The right to confirm whether we are processing their Personal Information and to obtain a copy of their Personal Information in a portable and, to the extent technically feasible, readily usable format.
* **Delete.** The right to delete their Personal Information provided to or obtained by us.
* **Correct.** The right to correct inaccuracies in their Personal Information, taking into account the nature and purposes of the processing of the personal information.
* **Opt-Out.** To opt out of certain types of processing, including: (i) to opt out of the “sale” of their Personal Information; (ii) to opt out of targeted advertising by us; and (iii) to opt out of any processing of Personal Information for purposes of making decisions that produce legal or similarly significant effects.

You may submit a request by emailing us as dpo@userstyles.org. When you submit a request, we will take steps to verify your identity and your request by matching the information provided by you with the information we have in our records. In some cases, we may request additional information in order to verify your identity, or where necessary to process your request. If we are unable to verify your identity after a good faith attempt, we may deny the request and, if so, will explain the basis for denial and how to remedy any deficiencies, where applicable.

To opt out of sales by us you can email us at: dpo@userstyles.org or at support@userstyles.org.

Authorized agents may initiate a request on behalf of another individual by contacting us at dpo@userstyles.org; authorized agents will be required to provide proof of their authorization and we may also require that the relevant consumer directly verify their identity and the authority of the authorized agent.
